Shraddha Arjun Sawant

Titwala -Thane, India shraddhasawant29@gmail.com

Profile

An Astute professional with nearly 13+ years of experience in Accounts, Finance, Majorly in Payables, and Receivables. Driven and Self-motivated and therefore effective at completing the task with minimal supervision. Confident and enthusiastic with a goal to make outstanding career progress.

Employment History

Nov 2021- Sep 2023

Associate at upGrad Education Pvt Ltd.

Job Description

- \cdot Manage the full accounts payable cycle from receipt of invoices/advances to payment, with high volume.
- · Identify, analyze, and resolve complex and escalated Procure to pay, which cannot be delivered due to existing issues.
- · Manage vendor relations and build effective partnerships.
- · Ensure all accounts payable policies and procedures are followed, including travel/employee claims and related expenses, vendor approval, and invoice processing.
- \cdot Bank Reconciliation & Monthly Provision entries.
- · Reconciliation of Vendor & Intercompany.
- · Handling Creditor's ageing & MIS.

Feb 2017-Oct 2021

Commercial Associate at Finance Plus India (A division of WPP)

Job Description

- · Verification & processing of Vendor Invoices/Employee Claims.
- · Addressing queries to vendors/OPCO in terms of Payment.
- \cdot Handling preparation of MIS reports and reconciliation statements.
- · Coordinating vendor empanelment.
- · TDS Calculation & Return e-Filing.

Details

A/303 Vakratunda Apartment Titwala East, 421605, India

Contact no- 9869830488.

Date of birth

29 September 1988

Marital Status: Single.

Skills

Data efficiency and accuracy

Fast Learner

Ability to lead a team.

Positivity Approach

Hobbies:

Traveling.

Cooking.

Learning new languages.

Reading.

Languages

Marathi

Hindi

English

Aug 2015-Feb 2017

Account Executive- MahaOnline Ltd

Job Description

- · Passing Day to day accounting entries.
- · Verification & processing of Vendor & Client Invoices.
- \cdot Daily collection of Payment Getway for various (government) services.
- · Handling of MIS and Reporting.
- · Bank Reconciliation & General ledgers
- · Vendor Payment (TDS and ST Calculation)

Sep 2010- Aug 2015

Junior Account Executive- Sharekhan Ltd

Job Description

- · Passing Day to day accounting entries.
- · Collection of Demat dues from client & branches.
- · Pay In and Payouts of Offline Clients.
- · Bank Reconciliation.
- . Handling Queries of Clients/Branch/ Franchisee

Feb 2010 – Sep 2010

Audit Assistant - S Panse & Co

Job Description

- \cdot Verification of Net Asset Value (NAV) calculation for all Funds schemes
- · Limit Monitoring as per IRDA Guidelines and internal SOP
- · Aid in various audits.

Education

- · TYB.com with 1st Class from Gurukul College of commerce Ghatkopar (E), March 2009, Mumbai.
- · HSC with 1st Class from Gurukul College of commerce Ghatkopar (E), Feb 2006, Mumbai.
- SSC with 2nd Class from Saraswati Vidya Mandir Ghatkopar (W), March 2004, Mumbai